Captioning Provided By:
MTV Networks
字幕提供者：
MTV网络
Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
Squidward: ♪ La-la-da-da-da,
da-dum ♪
章鱼哥：♪ 啦-啦-哒-哒-哒，
达达姆♪
♪ La-la-la, da-dum-dum ♪
♪ 啦啦啦，哒哒哒哒 ♪
♪ La-la-la, da-da-da-dum ♪
♪ Dum-dum-dum, dee-dee-dee ♪
♪ 达姆达姆，迪迪迪迪 ♪
♪ La-la-la, da-da-da-dum ♪
♪ 啦啦啦，哒哒哒哒 ♪
♪ Dum-de-dee, dum-de-dee ♪
♪ 杜姆-德-迪，杜姆-德-迪 ♪
♪ La-la-da, da-da-da-doo ♪
♪ 啦啦哒，哒哒哒哒 ♪
♪ Da-da-doo, dee-dee ♪
♪ 哒哒哒，迪迪 ♪
Hello, and welcome one and all
to a super-special episode of
"House Fancy."
您好，欢迎大家
到一个超级特别的情节
“房子的幻想。”
I'm your host, Nicholas Withers.
我是主持人尼古拉斯·威瑟斯。
Our first very special guest
on today's show will be
none other than...
我们的第一位非常特别的客人
在今天的节目中将会
不是别人，正是……
Hello?
你好？
Uh, hello?
呃，你好？
Ah...
啊...
Hello.
你好。
Man: Hello.
男：你好。
This isn't Squilliam Fancy-son
这不是斯奎利姆花哨的儿子
my lifelong rival who I met in
high school band class, is it?
我一生的对手
高中乐队课，是吗？
The same.
相同。
You wouldn't happen to be
watching "House Fancy",
would you?
你不会碰巧是
观看《奇幻之家》时，
你会吗？
I was, until you called.
我是，直到你打来电话。
Well, Squiddy,
I enjoy our chats,
but my catered lunch awaits.
嗯，鱿鱼，
我很享受我们的聊天
但我准备的午餐正在等待着。
And you know how hard
being fabulous is
on an empty stomach  .
你知道有多难
令人难以置信的是
空腹时。
Wait, why did you ask me if
I was watching "House Fancy"?
等等，你为什么问我是否
我在看《梦幻之家》？
Sorry, Squilliam, but we've
gotta get back to the show.
抱歉，斯奎利姆，但我们已经
得回去表演了。
Who's that talking
in the background?
是谁在说话
在后台？
Oh, I'm dreadfully
sorry, Nicky dear.
哦，我太可怕了
对不起，亲爱的尼基。
Well, toodle-ooh, Squidward.
嗯，哦，章鱼哥。
Enjoy the program.
享受这个节目。
Withers: OK, folks,
we'll be right back after
these important messages.
威瑟斯：好的，各位，
我们很快就会回来
这些重要信息。
Welcome back to "House Fancy,"
I'm Nicholas Withers.
欢迎回到“梦幻之家”，
我是尼古拉斯·威瑟斯。
Here next to me
is Squilliam Fancy-son.
在我旁边
是斯奎利亚姆·花式之子。
Hello, peasants.
哈喽，农民们。
Let me start by saying
what a lovely facade
you have, Mr. Fancy-son.
让我首先说
多么可爱的门面啊
你有，花式儿子先生。
Why, thank you, Nick.
为什么，谢谢你，尼克。
And your house doesn't look
too bad, either  .
而你的房子看起来并不
也太糟糕了。
Oh, Nicky.
哦，尼基。
Camera crew, can we get
a shot of Mr. Fancy-son's
fabulous house, please?
摄制组，我们可以得到
Fancy-son先生的一张照片
很棒的房子，好吗？
Hey, that's no better
than my house.
嘿，这再好不过了
比我家的。
I bid you welcome...
to my foyer.
我向你表示欢迎...
到我的门厅。
It's simply glorious.
这简直就是光荣的。
It truly is, Nicky.
确实如此，尼基。
It's like I've died
and gone to fancy heaven.
就好像我已经死了一样
然后去了幻想的天堂。
Is that what I think it is?
是我想的那样吗？
It sure is.
确实如此。
It's a gilded doorknob.
这是一个镀金的门把手。
Absolutely magical.
绝对神奇。
Absolutely imported.
绝对进口。
May I?
我可以？
But of course.
当然。
Oh... Lovely.
哦...可爱。
Isn't it?
不是吗？
Well, I have to say, Squilliam,
and I think I'm speaking for
好吧，我不得不说，斯奎利姆，
我想我是在代表
all of our viewers out there
when I'm saying this.
我们所有的观众
当我说这句话的时候。
You are truly a fancy man.
你真是一个花心的人。
Oh, well.
那好吧。
All this gushing
is perfectly deserved.
这一切都涌出
是完全应得的。
And now, I would
like to present to you
而现在，我愿意
喜欢呈现给你
my favorite room in the house.
房子里我最喜欢的房间。
It's all custom.
这都是定制的。
Look at this.
看看这个。
It's my jewel-encrusted
toilet paper holder.
这是我的镶满宝石的
卫生纸架。
Such class.
这样的班级。
Come, let me
show you... the roof.
来吧，让我
给你看...屋顶。
An elevator?
电梯？
Watch your step.
注意你的脚步。
This may take a while,
just sit back and relax.
这可能需要一段时间，
坐下来放松一下。
What the?
什么？
A whirlpool bath elevator?
漩涡浴缸电梯？
I brought some soap.
我带了一些肥皂。
All ashore.
全部上岸。
Welcome to my rooftop garden.
欢迎来到我的屋顶花园。
Romantic grotto...
浪漫的石窟...
sparkling, berry,
mineral-soda waterfall...
闪闪发光，浆果，
矿泉水瀑布...
and my personal favorite...
以及我个人最喜欢的...
a 130-foot-long
sculpture of my unibrow.
130英尺长
我的一字眉雕塑。
It's huge and lifelike.
它巨大而栩栩如生。
If you look closely,
you'll notice it's made entirely
out of gilded doorknobs.
如果你仔细观察，
你会发现它是完全制成的
从镀金的门把手中。
You have the fanciest...
你有最奇特的...
Eh, what?
呃，什么？
You have the fanciest...
你有最奇特的...
I have the fanciest ring?
我有最漂亮的戒指吗？
No, your phone is ringing.
不，你的电话响了。
Oh.
哦。
Hello?
你好？
Oh, yeah, hang on.
哦，是的，坚持住。
Uh, it's for you.
呃，这是给你的。
Hello, hello?
喂，喂？
Hello?
你好？
Hello.
你好。
My name is Squidward Tentacles.
我的名字是章鱼触手。
And my house is  far  fancier
than that slob Squilliam's.
我的房子要漂亮得多
比那个邋遢的斯奎利姆的还要多。
Really?
真的吗？
Really.
真的。
OK, we'll be at your house
in two hours with a camera crew.
好的，我们会去你家
与摄制组一起在两个小时内完成。
Two hours?
两个小时？
But I haven't even had time
to wash my hair.
但我还没来得及
洗头发。
There's a stain
on the rug.
有一个污点
在地毯上。
Uh, uh, ah, I'll use this chair
to hide it.
呃呃呃，我就用这把椅子
隐藏它。
There we go.
我们开始吧。
Now I'll just...  .
现在我就……
There's a hideous hole
in that wall.
有一个可怕的洞
在那堵墙里。
I'll just use this painting
to cover it up.
我就用这幅画
来掩盖它。
Perfect.
完美的。
No, no!
不，不！
Oh, I'll never get this place
in shape in time.
噢，我永远也得不到这个地方
及时成形。
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
How long have you
been spying on me?
你有多久了
一直在监视我吗？
Um... What day is it today?
嗯……今天是什么日子？
It's the day you go away
and never come back.
这是你离开的那一天
永远不会回来。
But Squidward, if I do that
但是章鱼哥，如果我这么做的话
then how am I gonna
help you get your house ready
for the  big  T.V. show?
那我该怎么办
帮助你准备好你的房子
为了大型电视节目？
How did you know about that?
你是怎么知道的？
I was spying on you.
我在监视你。
You want me to get
the cops down here again?
你想让我得到
警察又来了？
Because...
因为...
All right, fine.
好吧，好吧。
One slip up, and you are
out of here,  comprendo?
一失足，你就
离开这里，明白吗？
Mucho comprendo,
Señor Habanero.
非常理解，
哈瓦那先生。
All right first I'm gonna
give you something  so  simple
好吧，我先去
给你一些如此简单的东西
a person without a brain
could even get it done right.
一个没有大脑的人
甚至可以把事情做好。
Hoo, that's good,
'cause I lent my brain
to Patrick for the weekend.
呵呵，这样就好了
因为我借出了我的大脑
去帕特里克度周末。
Really?
真的吗？
No, not really.
不，不是真的。
He traded me these
two chocolate bars for it.
他用这些交换了我
两块巧克力。
I don't care.
我不在乎。
Just use this paint to cover up
that faded part
on the wall right there.
用这个油漆遮盖就可以了
那个褪色的部分
就在那儿的墙上。
Don't touch anything else.
不要碰其他任何东西。
OK.
好的。
SpongeBob, what was that noise?
海绵宝宝，那是什么声音？
Skin me alive
and drench me in boiling oil!
活剥我的皮
把我浸入滚烫的油里！
What have you done
to my living room?
你做了什么
到我的客厅？
I told you just to
paint the faded spot.
我告诉过你只是为了
涂上褪色的地方。
Well, it all looked
kind of faded.
好吧，这一切看起来
有点褪色了。
Never mind.
没关系。
Maybe it won't
show up on camera.
也许不会
出现在相机上。
Here, help me move this sofa.
来，帮我搬一下这张沙发。
You got it, Squiddy,
where are we moving her to?
你明白了，鱿鱼，
我们要把她搬到哪里去？
Hang on, I'm trying to get
a grip on the thing.
等一下，我正在努力争取
抓住事物。
Now don't move it till I say...
现在别动它，直到我说……
Ow!
噢！
OK, it's on my foot, I don't...
好吧，它在我的脚上，我不...
Ow!
噢！
OK...
好的...
Squidward: Ow!
章鱼哥：噢！
SpongeBob, I told you
not to move it till I said...
海绵宝宝，我告诉过你了
不要动它，直到我说...
Why do you keep moving it?
你为什么一直动它？
'Cause you keep saying, "Ow!"
因为你总是说：“噢！”
I don't need you,
I can move it myself.
我不需要你，
我自己可以搬。
Wow, Squidward,
you're so strong.
哇，章鱼哥，
你太坚强了。
And you split your sofa in half.
然后你把沙发分成两半。
It'll be really easy
to move now.
这会很容易
现在就搬家。
Oh, no, they're already here.
哦，不，他们已经来了。
Go get a vacuum to clean up
all the sofa bits.
去拿吸尘器来清理一下
所有的沙发碎片。
I gotta run upstairs
and dress my wound.
我得跑上楼
并包扎我的伤口。
Roger.
罗杰.
OK, Squidward, found the vacuum.
好的，章鱼哥，找到了真空。
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
Well, I'll just vacuum for him.
好吧，我就帮他吸尘吧。
Hmm, Squidward's house
is really messy.
嗯，章鱼哥的家
真的很乱。
I'm gonna need some extra power.
我需要一些额外的力量。
OK, SpongeBob, I finished-
What the?
好吧，海绵宝宝，我完成了——
什么？
Don't worry, Squidward,
I'll turn it off.
别担心，章鱼哥
我会把它关掉。
Come out of there.
从那里出来。
Uh, hang on, please.
呃，请坚持住。
Please, just one more
minute, Nick.
请再多一张
分钟，尼克。
Who's Nick?
尼克是谁？
Sorry, Squidward,
I couldn't wait any longer.
对不起，章鱼哥，
我不能再等了。
I gotta use your toilet,
no questions, thanks.
我得用你的厕所
没有问题，谢谢。
Whoo.
呼。
I wouldn't go in there
for a couple days.
我不会进去的
几天了。
Or weeks.
或者几周。
Please, please...
拜托，拜托...
Somebody put me
out of my misery.
有人把我
出于我的痛苦。
Have mercy on my soul...
怜悯我的灵魂...
Oh, hey, Squidward.
哦，嘿，章鱼哥。
If you see SpongeBob,
can you give him his brain back?
如果你看到海绵宝宝
你能把大脑还给他吗？
I was borrowing it
for the weekend.
我是借的
周末。
I'll just set it, uh, here.
我就设置一下，呃，这里。
See you.
再见。
Thank you, Patrick.
谢谢你，帕特里克。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Hello, and welcome back
to "House Fancy."
你好，欢迎回来
到“幻想之家”。
We're arriving at the home of
a Mr. Squidward Tentacles
我们即将抵达
章鱼哥先生的触手
who claims his house
is far fancier than that of
Squilliam Fancy-son.
谁声称拥有他的房子
远比
斯奎利亚姆，花哨的儿子。
Let's take a look.
我们来看一下。
Well, I, uh, um, I-I-I, I'm not
quite sure how to say this.
嗯，我，呃，嗯，我-我-我，我不是
很确定该怎么说。
Go ahead, say it.
来吧，说吧。
Withers: Squidward Tentacles,
you seem to have ushered in
凋灵：章鱼触手，
你似乎迎来了
an entire new era
in house fanciness.
一个全新的时代
在室内幻想中。
Huh?
啊？
I have... I have?
我有……我有？
What you have done here harkens
back to the illustrious
你在这里所做的事令人耳目一新
回到辉煌
post-primitive movement
popularized by famous designer
Sol Limpkins.
后原始运动
被著名设计师所推崇
索尔·林普金斯。
Say, was he a big
inspiration for you?
说吧，他是个大人物吗？
对你有启发吗？
Why, yes.
为什么，是的。
I've studied him for... years.
我研究他已经……很多年了。
I would like to announce
that Squidward's house
我想宣布
那个章鱼哥的房子
will be featured in
an hour-long, commercial-free
"House Fancy" special.
将出现在
时长一小时，无广告
特别版“House Fancy”。
And... Squidward will be crowned
"House Fancy" Prince of the Year
而且......章鱼哥将加冕
“House Fancy”年度王子
an honor which was originally
to be bestowed upon Squilliam
原本是一种荣誉
被授予斯奎利姆
but,  , now isn't.
但是，现在不是。
Oh, don't worry, Squilliam.
哦，别担心，斯奎利姆。
I might be able to get Squidward
to help you redecorate.
我也许能得到章鱼哥
来帮助您重新装修。
He is a personal friend of mine.
他是我的私人朋友。
You know success
hasn't gone to his head?
你知道成功
还没到他的头上吗？
He is still the same, old,
great guy, he has not changed.
他还是老样子，
伟大的家伙，他没有改变。
And this is
the maximum-security level.
这是
最高安全级别。
Since this is your first day,
I'll let you peek at
our number-one inmate.
由于这是您的第一天，
我让你看看
我们的头号囚犯。
He's too dangerous
to let him around
the other inmates.
他太危险了
让他四处走动
其他囚犯。
Why, what'd he do, rob a bank?
为什么，他做了什么，抢劫银行？
Worse, he tried to steal
the Krabby Patty formula.
更糟糕的是，他还试图偷窃
蟹黄饼配方。
Oh, OK...
哦，好吧……
So that's why we keep him
behind these impenetrable,
six-inch steel doors.
所以这就是我们留住他的原因
在这些难以捉摸的背后，
六英寸钢门。
'Course, it helps to lock it.
当然，锁定它会有所帮助。
He's gone.
他走了。
He's so small,
he could be anywhere.
他那么小，
他可以在任何地方。
He could be right
under our noses.
他可能是对的
在我们眼皮底下。
Uh, Frank, where's
your moustache?
呃，弗兰克，在哪里
你的小胡子？
Those fools'll
never find me now.
那些傻瓜会
现在再也找不到我了。
Aw, come on, baby, you know
how long I've been in the stir.
噢，来吧，宝贝，你知道的
我已经有多久了。
Woman: Get out.
女：出去吧。
And stay out,
you two-time loser.
并留在外面，
你这个两次失败者。
After everything
I've done for you.
一切之后
我已经为你做了。
Woman: Beat it, you jail-bird,
and take all your junk too.
女人：打住吧，你这个囚徒，
并带走所有的垃圾。
Well, that's just great.
嗯，那太好了。
Hey, it's my old guitar.
嘿，这是我的旧吉他。
I used to play it when I was
in that band as a kid.
我小时候也玩过
小时候在那个乐队里。
Man, those were good times.
伙计，那是美好时光。
OK, everybody.
好的，大家。
One, two, a-one-two-three.
一、二、一一二三。
You know, I don't think
I've had any good times.
你知道，我不认为
我曾经有过美好的时光。
SpongeBob: ♪ Oh, I wish I was
frying up some Krabby Patties ♪
海绵宝宝：♪哦，我希望我是
煎一些蟹肉饼 ♪
♪ That's what I really
love to do ♪
♪ 这就是我真正的想法
喜欢做♪
♪ Take a cup full of
boo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ 拿一杯满满的
呜呜呜 ♪
♪ And a pinch of awoogah ♪
♪ 还有一点 awoogah ♪
♪ A teaspoon of
♪
♪ 一茶匙
He's singing about
the Krabby Patty.
他唱的是关于
蟹肉饼。
If I could just get him
to explain that song
如果我能得到他就好了
解释那首歌
I'll have
the Krabby Patty formula.
我会有
蟹黄饼配方。
♪ Mix in some... ♪
♪ 混合一些... ♪
Hi, SpongeBob.
嗨，海绵宝宝。
That's a real nice song.
这真是一首好听的歌。
♪ Add a splash of whee... ♪
♪ 添加一点点…♪
But could you explain
those "whee" parts?
但你能解释一下吗
那些“哇”的部分？
♪ And when I'm done,
I chop up some ♪
♪ 当我完成后，
我切了一些♪
♪ Oh, oh-oh, oh-oh... ♪
♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦，哦...♪
Are you out of your mind?
你疯了吗？
Uh, I mean, that was
a delightful song
you were singing.
呃，我是说，那是
一首令人愉快的歌曲
你在唱歌。
Thanks, Plankton.
谢谢，浮游生物。
Mr. Krabs makes me censor out
all the patty ingredients
from my lyrics.
蟹老板让我审查
所有肉饼配料
从我的歌词中。
Oh, that's terrible.
哦，那太可怕了。
Krabs shouldn't stifle
a true artist like you.
螃蟹不应该窒息
像你这样真正的艺术家。
Go ahead and sing
your patty song uncensored.
继续唱歌吧
你的帕蒂歌曲未经审查。
I know
what you're doing.
我知道
你在做什么。
What, me, I'm not trying
to steal the patty formula.
什么，我，我不努力
窃取肉饼配方。
You want me to...
join your band.
你要我...
加入你的乐队。
What band, I don't have a band.
什么乐队，我没有乐队。
Oh, but you can't fool me.
噢，但你骗不了我。
Not when you got an awesome
guitar like that.
不是当你有一个很棒的
吉他之类的。
And only a true rocker
would have hair as greasy
and nasty as yours.
只有真正的摇滚乐手
头发会很油腻
和你一样令人讨厌。
It'll be so cool, we could
write songs together.
太酷了，我们可以
一起写歌。
Songs?
歌曲？
Yes.
是的。
And you can teach me
your Krabby Patty songs.
你可以教我
你的克拉比帕蒂歌曲。
Yay.
耶。
Come on, let's go
get our band together.
来吧，我们走吧
让我们的乐队聚在一起。
Patrick, Patrick.
帕特里克，帕特里克。
SpongeBob, SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝，海绵宝宝。
Patrick, I've got big news.
帕特里克，我有一个大消息。
Me too, me too.
我也是，我也是。
What's your news?
你有什么消息吗？
I found out where
boogers  come from.
我发现在哪里
鼻屎来自。
Ew, really?
呃，真的吗？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
What's your news?
你有什么消息吗？
Plankton just asked me
to join his rock-n-roll band.
浮游生物刚刚问我
加入他的摇滚乐队。
Can Patrick join our band?
帕特里克可以加入我们的乐队吗？
Sure, whatever.
当然，无论如何。
Hear that, Patrick, you're in.
听着，帕特里克，你进来了。
All right.
好的。
I play a mean belly.
我玩的是卑鄙的肚子。
Wow, Patrick,
we're gonna be famous!
哇，帕特里克，
我们会出名的！
Give me a break.
让我休息一下。
You don't know
anything about music.
你不知道
关于音乐的任何事情。
Too bad you're not
a musical genius.
可惜你不是
音乐天才。
Like me.
像我这样的。
SpongeBob: Oh, Squidward...
海绵宝宝：噢，章鱼哥……
What the...
什么...
Well, I  could  help you.
嗯，我可以帮助你。
But I wouldn't soil my art
playing rock-n-roll.
但我不会玷污我的艺术
玩摇滚乐。
Dressing all in black,
wearing boots covered in spikes
一身黑衣打扮，
穿着布满尖刺的靴子
playing enormous stadiums
filled with screaming,
adoring fans...
在巨大的体育场进行比赛
充满了尖叫声，
崇拜的粉丝...
clapping, demanding encores...
鼓掌，要求加演……
cheering me...
为我加油...
Oh, uh, changed my mind.
哦，呃，我改变主意了。
I'll join your band
and help you bottom-feeders.
我会加入你的乐队
并帮助你底层饲养者。
But I gotta get in shape first.
但我得先把身材练好。
Isn't this great, Plankton,
Squidward is gonna help us.
这不是很棒吗，浮游生物，
章鱼哥会帮助我们的。
Hmm?
唔？
Uh, yeah, great.
呃，是的，太棒了。
You know, Patrick,
being in a band
你知道，帕特里克，
在乐队中
gives you the liberty
to dress with a little more...
Uh, how should I put this?
给你自由
to dress with a little more...
Uh, how should I put this?
Yeah?
是的？
Well, with just a little more...
好吧，还有一点……
Go ahead, say it, SpongeBob.
说吧，海绵宝宝。
You know, pizzazz.
你知道，活力四射。
Perhaps
you didn't notice...
也许
你没有注意到...
my new hairdo.
我的新发型。
SpongeBob: Whoa-ho-ho,
I stand corrected.
海绵宝宝：哇喔喔，
我纠正了。
And unlike your
nasty, little wig...
与你不同的是
讨厌的小假发……
Mine is real.
我的是真的。
Man, how'd you
grow that so fast?
伙计，你怎么样
长得这么快？
Natural talent, watch this...
天赋异禀，看这个……
Whoo, yeah!
呼，是啊！
Dig that fancy follicle work.
挖掘那个奇特的毛囊工作。
Hey, check this one out.
嘿，看看这个。
Oh, man, Squidward's
not gonna want to miss this.
哦，伙计，章鱼哥的
不想错过这个。
Squidward: Hello?
章鱼哥：喂？
Hi, Squidward, aren't you
coming to band practice?
嗨，章鱼哥，是吗？
来参加乐队排练吗？
Are you kidding?
你在开玩笑吧？
I've got a lot of work to do
before I'm famous.
我有很多工作要做
在我出名之前。
OK, then,
we'll keep your seat warm.
好吧，那么，
我们会为您的座位保暖。
Patrick?
帕特里克？
I'm on it.
我正在做。
Greetings, fellow band-mates.
问候，乐队伙伴们。
Hey, Plankton, what's that?
嘿，浮游生物，那是什么？
T-shirts.
T 恤。
Ooh.
哦。
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy...
哦，男孩，哦，男孩，哦，男孩……
Ah, "Plankton and the...
啊，“浮游生物和……
Patty Stealers"?
偷帕蒂的人”？
Uh, if you guys
don't like the name, uh...
呃，如果你们
不喜欢这个名字，呃...
I...
我...
Love it!
爱它！
Kind of vague and mysterious.
有点模糊又神秘。
Can I get mine in pink?
我可以买粉色的吗？
It looks like a tattoo.
它看起来像一个纹身。
Hey, Plankton, can our
first song go like this?
嘿，浮游生物，我们可以吗？
第一首歌是这样的吗？
And then turn into one of
those songs that goes...
然后变成其中之一
那些歌曲...
Yes, perfect, now all we need
are the lyrics.
是的，完美，现在我们需要的一切
是歌词。
You know, something personal.
你知道，一些个人的事情。
Maybe a secret you know,
or a favorite recipe, hmm?
或许有你知道的秘密
或者最喜欢的食谱，嗯？
Or... One about
my new friend Plankton?
或者...一个关于
我的新朋友浮游生物？
Or the adventures of...
或者说是冒险……
Stop it,  .
别说了，。
The best kind of lyrics
are the ones that are
deep and revealing.
最好的歌词
是那些
深刻而富有启发性。
Something only you know?
有什么只有你知道的事？
Secret recipe.
秘方。
I once searched for
my innermost secrets.
我曾经寻找过
我内心深处的秘密。
All I found was this.
我发现的只有这个。
Is that what
you mean, Plankton?
是这样吗
你是说，浮游生物？
SpongeBob: What is that?
海绵宝宝：那是什么？
It's my, uh,
recording equipment.
这是我的，呃，
录音设备。
Oh, my gosh, what do I do?
哦，天哪，我该怎么办？
Just take a seat here,
and I'll strap you in.
就在这里坐吧，
我会把你绑起来。
Now just relax and let
the equipment do its job.
现在放松并让
设备发挥其作用。
Now let's see what's
locked in his subconscious.
现在让我们看看是什么
锁在他的潜意识里。
♪ Time to feed him,
time to feed him,
now it's Gary's feeding time ♪
♪ 是时候喂他了，
有时间喂他，
现在是加里的喂食时间♪
Nope.
没有。
♪ Brush, brush, brush my teeth,
gently keep them clean ♪
♪ 刷牙，刷牙，刷牙，
轻轻地保持它们清洁♪
The Krabby Patty formula's
gotta be in here somewhere.
蟹黄饼配方的
一定在这儿的某个地方。
What's going-  ...
这是怎么回事——...
I'm a failure.
我是个失败者。
Cheer up, Plankton.
振作起来，浮游生物。
We've still got a whole week
before our first gig
at the Krusty Krab.
我们还有整整一周的时间
在我们的第一次演出之前
在蟹堡王。
At the Krusty Krab?
在蟹堡王？
Uh-huh, but old man Krabs
doesn't want us bugging
the customers.
嗯嗯，但是螃蟹老头
不想让我们打扰
客户。
So we have to go in after hours
when nobody's there.
所以我们必须在下班后进去
当没人在的时候。
When nobody's there?
当没人的时候？
My perfect dream-body.
我完美的梦想身体。
Narrator: One week later...
旁白：一周后……
Oh, no, it's the cops,
I can't let them see me.
哦，不，是警察，
我不能让他们看到我。
Why?
为什么？
Uh, cops are autograph hounds.
呃，警察是签名猎犬。
Yeah, they're always after me.
是的，他们总是在追赶我。
Mm, that's tough.
嗯，这很难。
Don't worry, I'll hide you.
别担心，我会隐藏你的。
Hey, what are you kids
up to this late at night?
嘿，你们是什么孩子？
深夜都熬到这一步了？
We're on our way
to our first gig.
我们正在路上
到我们的第一场演出。
We're in a band.
我们在一个乐队里。
A band, huh, well, that's, uh...
乐队，呃，呃，那个……
Oh.
哦。
Uh, you've got a, uh...
呃，你有一个，呃...
Got a, uh, what  ?
有一个，呃，什么？
Uh... it's right...
呃……没错……
Yes  ?
是的  ？
Just keep your nose clean, kid.
保持你的鼻子干净，孩子。
Sure thing, officer.
当然可以，军官。
They're gone.
他们走了。
You will never
speak of this to anyone.
你永远不会
与任何人谈论这件事。
Come on, come on, hurry up.
来吧，来吧，快点。
SpongeBob: Don't worry,
I just need to get the key out.
海绵宝宝：别担心，
我只需要把钥匙拿出来。
Give me that,
you incompetent fool.
给我那个，
你这个无能的傻瓜。
Yes, the Krabby Patty
formula is mine.
是的，蟹肉饼
公式是我的。
Uh, I mean, we'll have
a great time.
呃，我是说，我们会有
一段美好的时光。
Now where does Krabs
keep that formula?
现在蟹蟹在哪里
保留那个公式吗？
Whoo, let's rock!
哇，让我们一起摇滚吧！
Yeah.
是的。
All right.
好的。
Squidward, are you ready?
章鱼哥，你准备好了吗？
I'm ready.
我准备好了。
OK.
好的。
Patrick, are you ready
帕特里克，你准备好了吗
Plankton, are you ready?
浮游生物，你准备好了吗？
Plankton?
浮游生物？
Plankton.
浮游生物。
Uh... I'm ready?
呃...我准备好了吗？
SpongeBob: Wait a minute...
海绵宝宝：等一下……
Was this band just a front
so you could steal
the Krabby Patty secret formula?
这支乐队只是一个幌子吗
这样你就可以偷东西
蟹黄派的秘密配方？
What, no, I was in it
for the music, man.
什么，不，我在里面
为了音乐，伙计。
Well, at least
I'm back to my old cell.
嗯，至少
我回到了原来的牢房。
Oh, no, you're not.
哦，不，你不是。
We've got a special
cell for you.
我们有一个特别的
为你准备的细胞。
But I liked my old cell.
但我喜欢我的旧手机。
Then you're gonna love this one.
那你一定会喜欢这个的。
SpongeBob: There's no time
to waste, Plankton.
海绵宝宝：没时间了
浪费，浮游生物。
We've only got 22 years
to practice before our next gig.
我们只有22年
在我们下一场演出之前练习。
A one and a two...
一个一，一个二……